Army with harmony
Dave drop a load on 'em
OPP, how can I explain it
I'll take you frame by frame it
To have why'all jumpin' shall we sayin' it
O is for Other, P is for People scratchin' temple
The last P...well...that's not that simple
It's sorta like another way to call a cat a kitten
It's five little letters that are missin' here
You get on occasion if the other party
isn't game 'n it seems I gotta start to explainin'
Bust it
You ever had a girl and met her on a nice hello
You get her name and number and then you feelin' real mellow
You get home, wait a day, she's what you want to know about then you call up and it's her girl friend or her cousin's house
It's not a front, F to the are to the O to the N to the T
It's just her boyfriend's at her house (Boy, that's what is scary)
It's OPP, time other people's what you get it.
There's no room for relationship there's just room to hit it
How many brothers out there know just what I'm gettin' at
Who thinks it's wrong ''cause I'm splittin' and co-hittin' that
Well if you do, that's OPP and you're not down with it
But if you don't, here's your membership
You down with OPP (Yeah you know me)
Who's down with OPP (Every last homie)
Who's down with OPP? (All the Homies)
As for the ladies, OPP means something gifted.
The first two letters are the same but the last is something different
It's the longest, loveliest, lean-- I call it the leanest.
It's another five letter word rhymin' with cleanest and meanest
I won't get into that, I'll do it...ah...sorta properly
I say the last P...hmmm...stands for property
Now lady here comes a kiss, blow a kiss back to me, now tell me exactly.
Have you ever known a brother who have another like ah girl or wife
And you just had to stop and just ''cause he look just as nice You looked at him, he looked at you and you knew right away.
That he had someone but he was gonna be yours anyway
You couldn't be seen with him and honestly you didn't care.
'Cause in a room behind a door no one but y'all are there
When y'all are finish, y'all can leave and only y'all would know.
And then y'all could throw the skeleton bones right in the closet do'
Now don't be shocked ''cause if you're down I want your hands up high
Say OPP (OPP) I like to say with pride
Now when you do it, do it well and make sure that it counts. You're now down with a discount
You down with OPP (Yeah you know me)
Who's down with OPP (Every last lady)
Who's down with OPP? (All the ladies)
This girl ah tried to OPP me
I had a girl and she knew that matter-of-fact my girl was partner's that.
Had a fall out, disagreement, yeah an argument.
She tried to do me so we did it in my apartment, bust it
That wasn't the thing it must have been the way she hit the ceiling.
'Cause after that she kept on coming back and catchin' feelings
I said, "Let's go my girl is coming so you gotta leave" She said, "Oh no, I love you Treach" I said, "Now child please"
You got's to leave, come grab your coat, right now you gotta go.
I said now look you choose the stairs or choose the stair window
This was a thing, a little thing, you shouldn't have put your heart
'Cause you know I was OPP, hell from the very start
Come on, come on, now let me tell you what it's all about.
When you get down, you can't go 'round runnin' off at the mouth
That's rule number one in this OPP establishment.
You keep your mouth shut and it won't get back to her or him
Exciting isn't it, a special kinda business
Many of you will catch the same sorta OPP is you with
Him or her for sure is going to admit it
When OPP comes, damn-- skippy I'm with it
You down with OPP (Yeah you know me)
Who's down with OPP? (It's a party)
Break it Down